

Info

- pellabeuf@gmail.com
- Paris, France
- In Linkedin
- Github
- Medium
- **X** X

Profile

With **5 years** of experience in full stack and blockchain development, I am a passionate and determined developer. My goal is to continue learning and excelling in the field of blockchain, in order to actively contribute to this rapidly expanding ecosystem.

Languages

French, English

Interests

Technology and Innovation Blockchain Finance Real Estate Sports

Foulques Pellabeuf

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

Technical Skills

Programming Languages

TypeScript Solidity NestJs Docker React/Next.js Database ۸۱۸/۵ Rust Tailwind Circom ORM Grafana Angular Noir-lang Elasticsearch Sequelize Hardhat/Forge Redis Bootstrap Prisma

Experiences

Morpho

2024 - Present

Subgraph

Blockchain Developer

I focus on developing and optimizing future versions of Morpho, leveraging **JavaScript-driven technologies** to enhance scalability, performance, and seamless integration.

GraphQL

Onbrane

2023 - 2024

Lead Blockchain Developer

I developed a decentralized financial application EVM for a financial company that has seen €5 trillion + exchanged, using cryptographic techniques such as ZKP and homomorphic encryption to ensure the privacy of debt products.

Hexalabs

2022 - 2023

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

I developed frontends with Next.js, deployed blockchain projects in Solidity (**DeFi, NFT Marketplace**, etc.), and built backends.

Toys films

2020 - 2022

Full Stack Developer

Education

Hetic university

2017 - 2020

Computer science bachelor

Training focused on real-time 3D content creation, covering **applied mathematics** and **web development**.